[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What kangaroo species set a record by moving with 64 kilometers per hour (40 mph)?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Eastern Grey Kangaroo", "Great Grey Kangaroo", "Forester Kangaroo"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Seismic waves are classified in four types - P-waves (primary), S-waves (secondary), Love waves (surface waves) and this type.", "correct_answer": "Rayleigh waves", "incorrect_answers": ["F-waves", "L-waves", "Richter waves"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Darth Vader only had one child.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "At what time of the year is the Tom and Jerry cocktail served traditionally in the United States?", "correct_answer": "Christmas", "incorrect_answers": ["Easter", "New Years Eve", "Thanksgiving"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie I, Robot Will Smith drove a very futuristic car designed especially for the movie, by this maker.", "correct_answer": "Audi", "incorrect_answers": ["Ferrari", "Renault", "Chrysler"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In Smokey and the Bandit, after Cletus and the Bandit win the bet, they take a double-or-nothing offer from Big and Little Enos to retrieve clam chowder from Boston.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Kingpin Bill Murrays character, Ernie McCracken, has a clear bowling ball with a skull in the middle of it.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the name of Fraisers fathers dog on the hit TV show set in Seattle?", "correct_answer": "Eddie", "incorrect_answers": ["Niles", "Marty", "Skip"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This is one of the fashion designers whose designs were included in Barbie Dolls collection of couture.", "correct_answer": "Gucci", "incorrect_answers": ["Yves Saint Laurent", "John Galiano", "Shiseido"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Caspian tiger is believed to have become extinct.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the capital of Australia?", "correct_answer": "Canberra", "incorrect_answers": ["Sydney", "Melbourne", "Ottawa"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the film The Da Vinci Code, when Sophie finds out that she is the heir to the royal blood, what miracle does she jokingly try to perform?", "correct_answer": "Walk on water", "incorrect_answers": ["Withering a fig tree", "Turn water into wine", "Part the sea"]}]